## **Lorraine Nue**

#21

5 pages

From:

Priscilla Cole <pcolesiah@yahoo.com>

Sent:

Tuesday, July 21, 2015 2:59 PM

To:

Church Office

Subject:

Cemetery Manager

**Attachments:** 

Detail Resume.doc; Recommendation Letter 1.doc; P Transcript.pdf; PRISCILLA COLLINS

also sent 9-page Transcript and 2 recommendation letters

REFERENCE.docx; cover ltr.docx

Hello Sir/Madam:

My name is Priscilla Collins. I would like to express my interest in the Cemetery Manager position. Attached to this email is my Resume, Cover letter, College transcript and Recommendation letter. If my qualifications match the open position please do not hesitate to call me at (202) 567-9786.

Thank you very much,

Priscilla S. Collins

Priscilla Siah Collins

1432 Bangor St. SE

Washington, D.C. 20020

Dear Sir/Madam,

The purpose of this cover letter is regarding my interest in a position as a Cemetery

Manager at St. Paul's at Rock Creek. With this letter, I want to express my interest and hopes of
gaining a position within your office. Accordingly, my complete resume is attached for your
review and consideration.

As a strong supervisor for three years, I have been recognized for my achievements through performance assessments documenting my outstanding job performance. My proven record of accomplishment, reliability, and my committed work ethic during my tenure as facilities manager to the corporate director contributed to our excellent service levels, reducing budget cost two years in a row, improving accuracy and reducing workload for the Facilities Team. I normally establish good working relationships with fellow co-workers, to whom I am always well known. When selected, my extreme positive professional attitude and ability to work well within a team atmosphere can only enhance the operations of the office.

I also hope to fulfill my educational long term goal of pursuing a MBA at George Mason University. In conclusion I welcome the opportunity to discuss how I might further contribute to your office.

Respectfully,

Priscilla Siah Collins

## PRISCILLA S. COLLINS

T: 202.567.9786 | Washington, D.C. | Email: pcolesiah@yahoo.com

## **RESUME**

Dedicated and technically skilled business professional with a versatile administrative support skill set developed through experience as an office manager, secretary and administrative assistant. Excel in resolving employer challenges with innovative solutions, systems and process improvements proven to increase efficiency, customer satisfaction and the bottom line. Offer advanced computer skills in MS Office Suite and other applications/systems.

## KEY SKILLS

- Office Management
- Teambuilding & Supervision
- Staff Development & Training

- Report & Document Preparation
- Spreadsheet & Database Creation
- Assist with Policy & Procedure Manuals

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## ACCESS INTELLIGENCE-MARKETING FIRM, Rockville, MD

Facilities Supervisor

(06/2011- Present)

Provide constant attention to all life safety issues; oversee vendor activities that include the scheduling of repair and maintenance needs as required. Ensure building emergency systems are operational through in-house inspections and vendor maintenance contracts. Seating and all related building components closely monitor progress to ensure quality of work, inspect janitorial service quality regularly. Provide clear direction and timely follow-up on issues. Accept and ship all packages such as UPS & FedEx, assist with various projects including company events, maintaining spreadsheets. Reserve conference rooms. Arrange transportation for those traveling through Regency. Prepare/set-up meeting rooms. Provide/order breakfast and lunch. Keep track of all those with dietary needs. Assist with events by printing out name tags. Arrange video conferencing. Support the CEO and various other managers daily. Manage busy calendars and process management expense reports. Work closely with contractors regarding lighting, plumbing HVAC issues. Work with Office Images, Zee Medical, Avison Young and DataWatch regarding activation/deactivation of access cards. Coordinate office relocation, orchestrated the office move. Maintain the phone system (Site Administration) while managing company phone directory. Webinar and conference call maintenance. Maintain all printers/copiers from MBS and Meridian Office Systems. Maintain phone systems in the Rockville office. Travel to other offices as needed.

## Capital Sports Complex, District Heights, MD

Front Desk Coordinator

(9/2009-10/2010)

Provided critical support to various managers daily. Maintained all filing. Prepared all memberships to be processed into the database. Trained all employees on database. Mail distribution and received packages from Federal Express, USPS and UPS. Worked closely with the finance department with preparing deposits. Answered all questions from top directors regarding major groups. Created, updated and maintained information center for manuals and schematics.

## Strayer University, Washington, DC

Admission Secretary

(10/2004-7/2008)

Supervised two Admission Associates. Reviewed and reconciled internet and telephone batch leads. Prepared and generated acceptance letters. Processed student I-20 to the Department of Homeland Security. Reconciliation reports processed and maintained database and finalized files for the purpose of audits. Took minutes for meetings. Ensured review and updated of merged records. Validation, copying and depositing of checks. Ensured all appropriate data is entered into 360 for a smooth month end process.

## Bork & Associates, Washington, DC

Legal Secretary

(03/2000-11/2002)

Prepared accounts Payable and Receivable, checks, cash, deposits, and invoices. Coordinated with the attorneys in expense reports inputs. Copied, stuff, seal, bind, mailed briefs, memorandum and retainers. Database maintenance. Answered all e-mails from clients in regards to inquiry, question, and other. Assisted with retrievals requested by coworkers for e-mail blasts. Maintained company contracts, imported into excel and entered into a database. Trained new employees on the database and set up security codes and passwords. Promulgate monthly reports for the Finance department. Sent announcement emails and updates company wide.

## Animal Clinic of Anacostia, Washington, DC

(02/2008 - Present)

Development Administrator

Processed acknowledgements of all walk-ins and appointments on weekend basis. Coordinated with the doctors regarding the treatment, vaccination and prescription of feline and canine patients. Database maintenance. Answered all phone and site questions. Assisted with retrievals requested by doctors and veterinarian technician. Trained new employees on the database and credit/debit card equipment. Organized files, security codes and passwords. Modify reports for the owner/President.

#### **EDUCATION**

# STRAYER UNIVERSITY Bachelor of Business Administration in Legal Studies, 2013

Thomas A. Duckenfield Legal Assistance Program Certificate of Completion, 2000

WASHINGTON LEE HIGH SCHOOL Diploma Received, 1997

#### SOFTWARE APPLICATIONS

Microsoft Suite including: Microsoft Word, Excel, Access, Outlook, PowerPoint VNC viewer/reader, Site Administration, Windows NT 4.0, Windows 98, Remote Link, Avaya Softconsole, phone system Spreadsheets, Adobe Acrobat, Salesforce